amen amen happy sabbath everyone
um
so as you can see for those of you who
are watching the sabbath school a little
bit earlier um
we are i i was
looking to see if the brothers could
join me for the sermon today but they
actually both have some things that they
have to take care of some bible studies
so um we will do that again at another
time
but uh today we're gonna be talking
about
uh last week in fact we we talked about
juicing the entire old testament today
we're going to juice the entire
new testament and so i'm just going to
ask for you to just bow your heads as we
pray once more
and then we're going to get into the
word of god today and this is going to
be more of a teaching sermon
in line with what we were discussing a
little bit earlier today in sabbath
school so
pray with me if you will please heavenly
father thank you lord for giving us this
opportunity
to share your word bless us lord is our
prayer in jesus name
amen all right
um
i'm gonna go ahead and share my screen
okay so
last week we we talked about
how the entire old testament was
um revealing the plan of salvation
particularly when it comes to the
sanctuary
message we saw last week
that the books of genesis to judges
covered what we described as the 70-week
prophecy
we saw that the books of joshua to
chronicles
covered what we paralleled in the new
testament as a 1260-year prophecy
and finally we saw that the books of
esther
uh ezra and nehemiah parallel the 2300
day prophecy
so i'm not going to go into that in any
detail today i just want to encourage
you
to check out the sermon from last week
okay check out the sermon from last week
today we're going to be doing the same
thing
but with the new testament
so i'm gonna just share with you right
up front
that um let's see here
all right my slides are not working give
me one second guys give me
one moment here
okay so
um let me go ahead and begin that repeat
that
um we're gonna be looking at the new
testament
we're gonna be looking at three phases
of the new testament hopefully you guys
can hear me
now we're gonna be looking at three
phases of the new testament
my powerpoint uh as i said what's new
is not uh not working so we're just
gonna
you can i will send you my powerpoint um
so you know you'll have access to this
okay
um the three sections we're going to be
looking at matthew mark luke and john is
phase one
phase two is a book of acts to
revelation chapter 11
and phase three is going to be
to revelation chapter 22.
revelation 11 to revelation 22.
those are the three phases we're going
gonna be covering as we
juice down the new testament so
let's begin with uh deuteronomy chapter
five we're not getting to the new
testament yet
i kind of want to build this this uh
theme for you
i first want to talk about the
description of sin the description of
sin and what we're going to be looking
at
is the entire plan of salvation today
so let's talk about the description of
sin for a moment in deuteronomy chapter
5 verse 22
the bible says these words the lord
spake unto all your assembly in the
mount
out of the midst of fire of the cloud
and of the thick darkness
and a great voice with a great voice and
he added no more
and he wrote them in two tables of stone
and delivered them unto me
so the bible here is talking about the
the the event where
moses is given the ten commandments
right god
speaks the ten commandments to moses and
the bible says
that he added no more these
are the laws of god the law of god
first john 3 4 tells us that whosoever
commits sin transgresses also the law
for sin is the transgression
of the law sin is the transgression
of the law so we understand that when
one sins they are transgressing the law
of god the 10 commandment law in fact
romans chapter 7 verse 7 says this what
shall we say then is the law
sin god forbid nay i had not known
sin but by the law for i had not known
lust except the law had said thou
shall not covet
so the bible lets us know here that the
ten commandments
is what describes sin
the ten commandments describes sin
and the bible tells us in romans chapter
six verse 23
that the wages of sin is
death the wages of sin is death so
the law of god prescribes or describes
sin
and the bible tells us the wages of sin
is death now i want to talk about the
prescription
for sin what was the prescription for
sin
in the old testament according to the
book of leviticus chapter 4 verse 20
the bible says and he shall do with the
bullock as he did with the bullock for a
sin offering
so shall he do with this and the priest
shall make an atonement for them and it
shall be
forgiven them in the old testament
the way one got forgiveness was
by the sacrifice of an animal
the shedding of blood so we can see this
the bible mentions this in leviticus 4
leviticus 4 31 leviticus 4 35
leviticus 5 10 leviticus 5 13
leviticus 5 16 5 18
leviticus 6 verse 7 and leviticus 19
verse 22.
all of it talks about the forgiveness of
sins
how you forgot how you how your sins
were forgiven
was by the shedding of blood
by the shedding of blood now
as we look at this process of how sins
were forgiven
we wanna i want you to notice
exodus chapter 12 verse 48 and 49
in exodus chapter 12 verse 48 and 49 the
bible says when a stranger shall adjourn
with thee
and will keep the passover to the lord
let all his males be circumcised
and let them come near and keep it and
he shall be as one that is born in the
land
for no uncircumcised person shall eat
thereof
one law shall be for him that is
homeborn and unto the stranger
that's adjourneth among you
so the bible tells us here that in order
for a gentile or a
stranger to keep these uh uh
to be able to exercise the process
whereby
forgiveness was gained they had to be
circumcised in order to keep these laws
so these laws included the ceremonial
feast days
um and of course all the sacrifices
all right so one of your following so
far
this was the old testament prescription
for sin you sinned in other words you
broke the law of god
the prescription was i gotta get an
animal sacrifice and sacrifice that
animal all right
so one if you are following
and you get that point okay
daniel chapter nine introduces us
to a new method
for the forgiveness of sin i'm going to
say this way
daniel 9 foretells of a new vaccine
for sin a new vaccine for sin
so i'm going to go ahead and read daniel
daniel 9 verse 24 onward this is known
as the
week prophecy what we have been
discussing in all our sabbath schools
for the last five six seven weeks
daniel 9 24 says this 70 weeks are
determined upon by people
and upon by holy city to finish the
transgression
to make an end of sins and to make
reconciliation for
iniquity and to bring in everlasting
righteousness
and to seal up the vision and prophecy
and to anoint the most holy
know therefore and understand that from
the going forth of the commandment to
restore and to build jerusalem
unto the messiah the prince there goes
your new vaccine
all right i want you to just catch this
for a moment
there goes the new vaccine the coming
of messiah the prince i'm going to go
ahead and keep reading verse 26.
and after three score in two weeks shall
messiah be cut off but not for himself
and the people of the prince that shall
come shall destroy the city and the
sanctuary
and the end thereof shall be with a
flood and unto the end
of the war desolations are determined
he shall confirm the covenant with many
for one week and in the midst of the
week he shall cause a sacrifice and
oblations to cease
and for the over spreading of the [\h__\h] of
abominations he shall make it desolate
notice this carefully even
unto the consummation
and that determined shall be poured out
upon
the desolate all right
i'm gonna come back to this verse and
address a few things but remember what
are we talking about today
we're talking about juicing the new
testament so remember what have we done
so far
we looked at the description of sin
what describes sin the law of god
the ten commandment law of god what was
the prescription for sin
in other words if you broke the law of
god the prescription for sin
was sacrifice an animal right
that was the prescription daniel 9
points to a new vaccine
and that vaccine would be the shed
blood of jesus
in light of that the entire
new testament is an unfolding
of this vaccine it is an unfolding
of this prophecy in daniel chapter 9.
it is an unfolding of the work the
messiah would do
to ultimately rid the
world of sin
so with that in my
one if you follow what i'm saying so far
i've just set the foundation all right
so let's go to the new testament we're
going to juice
the books of matthew mark luke and john
and we're going to do this very quickly
what are the books of matthew mark luke
and john about they are about
phase one of the vaccine
what is phase one of the vaccine it is
the production
of the vaccine christ
god himself became a man
came in the flesh to shed his blood
on our behalf
john 1 29 the bible says the next day
john sees
jesus coming unto him and saith behold
the lamb of god which taketh away
the sin of the world
the books of matthew mark luke and john
are basically describing to us
the production of the vaccine for sin
that is the blood of jesus christ
phase one listen carefully phase one
is the arrival
and production of the vaccine
now now ultimately what does this
vaccine
accomplish and if you want to know if
you should take the vaccine
yes you need to take this vaccine
you may question other vaccines this one
don't question i want you to notice two
things that this vaccine
will ultimately do in john 1 7 the bible
says but if we walk in the light
as he is in the light we have fellowship
one with another
and the blood of jesus christ his son
cleanses us from all sin so
number one this vaccine
is able to cleanse us from
how much sin
all sin all
sin that's what the vaccine does number
two
according to revelation 12 11 the bible
says and they overcame
him by the blood of the
lamb overcame who they're talking about
the dragon we're talking about satan
so listen carefully the blood serves two
purposes number one
to cleanse us from sin and number two
to overcome satan
those are the two things we see that
this blood is
going to do this vaccine is going to do
i want you to notice something else in
colossians 2 verse 10
and 11 the bible says and you are
completing him
which is the head of all principality
and power
in whom also you are circumcised
with the circumcision made without hands
and
putting off the body of sins of the
flesh by the circumcision of
christ all right let me rephrase this
when we accept christ he becomes our
circumcision
so listen carefully
in the old testament the description of
sin was the law of god
the prescription for sin were the
ceremonial laws
but in order to get access to exercise
those ceremonial laws
you have to be circumcised you have to
be circumcised
and then keep the law the ceremonial law
that would enable you to be forgiven
for the law of god which is the
description of sin
in the new testament there's a new
vaccine
it is the blood of christ and in order
to get access to that
you still have to be circumcised but it
is not a circumcision after the flesh
it is the circumcision of jesus christ
all right one if you're following
what i'm saying so far one if this
makes sense
all right
the vaccine
of jesus christ his
blood is going to do
two things deliver us
from sin and then deliver us
from satan so if you're wondering if you
should take
this vaccine
you need to take this vaccine
again you may question other vaccines
but beloved the blood of christ is a
vaccine that you must have
so the books of matthew mark luke and
john basically
are showing phase one of
of this vaccination against sin and it
is
the blood of jesus now we need to
address
phase two what is phase two
according to hebrews 9 verse 11 and 12
the bible says but christ
being come and a high priest of good
things to come
by a greater and more perfect tabernacle
not made with hands
that is to say not of this building
neither by the blood of goats
and calves but by his own blood
he entered in once into the holy place
having obtained eternal redemption
for us so listen carefully
the second phase of this vaccine
is the administration of the vaccine
by our high priest jesus christ
phase one was the production of the
vaccine
christ on the cross shedding his blood
this is what the 70-week prophecy was
pointing to
matthew mark luke and john point to the
coming messiah
who shed his blood to produce or provide
the vaccine that would be necessary
to save us from sin
phase two of that is the administration
of the vaccine in other words the
vaccine has to be given
and how would it be given christ ascends
into heaven
as our high priest to minister
his blood in our behalf
where does he enter in the sanctuary he
enters into the holy place
this is why revelation 11 verse 12 or
revelation 1 verse 12
says this and i turned to see the voice
that spake with me and being turned
i saw seven golden candlesticks where
does john
see jesus he sees them in the holy place
in the midst of
seven golden candlesticks and then you
have the seven churches that's
revelation one two and three
in revelation four and five we see this
four verse five the bible says and out
of the throne precedes lightnings and
thunderings and voices
and there were seven lamps of fire
burning before the throne
which are the seven spirits of god and
then you have the unfolding of the
seven seals which is from revelation
uh uh four all the way up to revelation
chapter eight
then we see in revelation eight verse
three john
sees an angel standing by a golden
censor
standing by the altar of incense which
is again
in the holy place and then you have the
unfolding of the
seven trumpets which takes us all the
way to revelation chapter 11.
so let me recap this for you
if matthew mark luke and john
describes christ coming to this earth
and
shedding his blood for us in the outer
court
to provide the vaccine
of his blood to produce the vaccine of
his blood
then from the book of acts
where we have jesus ascending into
heaven
into the holy place phase of his
ministry
all the way through to revelation
chapter
11 is all covering
holy place ministry
and that holy place ministry is the
second phase of this
vaccination it is christ administering
his blood on our behalf for a
very specific reason and i need you to
follow this carefully
because in acts chapter 2 and verse 38
peter says these words
then peter said unto them repent and be
baptized every one of you in the name of
jesus christ
for the remission
of sins and you shall receive
the gift of the holy ghost so what is
peter here preaching
he is now preaching the remission
of sins good news
everyone the vaccine
of christ's blood puts you
in remission how many of you
rejoice that you are in remission
one if you can say yes i
understand whoa the blood of christ
the vaccine has put me in remission
of sins
it is a good thing to be in remission
we should rejoice the bible is letting
us know
the second phase of christ's ministry
is the phase of remission the remission
of sins romans 3 25 puts it this way
speaking of christ it says whom god has
set forth to be a propitiation
through faith in his blood to declare
his righteousness for the remission
of sins that are passed through the
forbearance of god
do you see this the blood of christ
the vaccine of christ in its
second first phase the production of the
vaccine
second phase remission of sins
administered by our high priest
in his holy place phase
of ministry this is why hebrews 9 22
tells us
and almost all things are by the law of
purge with blood and without the
shedding of blood
there is no remission
hebrews 10 18 now where remission of
these is
there is no more offering for sin christ
offered himself
for us one time and that offering
provides us now with remission
of our sins
in the old testament the vaccine
the prescription for sin was the killing
of an animal
in the new testament the vaccine
for sin is the blood of the lamb
which gives us remission
from sin
in the book of ephesians chapter 2 we're
told this verse 11
wherefore remember that you being in
time past gentiles
in the flesh who are called
uncircumcision
by that which is called the circumcision
in the flesh made by hands
that at time at that time you are
without christ
being aliens from the commonwealth of
israel and strangers from the covenants
of promise
having no hope and without god in the
world but now
in christ jesus you
who are sometimes afar off are made
nigh by the blood of
christ for he is our peace
and has made both one and has broken
down the wall
middle wall of partition between us
having abolished in his flesh
the enmity even the law of commandments
contained in ordinances
in other words beloved the blood of the
lamb
the vaccine of christ replaces
the old testament prescription for sin
that's why we don't we no longer need to
keep these ceremonial feast days
or these ceremonial sabbaths we no
longer no longer need to
sacrifice animals but the the
description for sin
still is the description for sin
i'm simply wanting you to understand
beloved the plan of salvation
and how it works particularly the blood
of jesus i
see some of y'all thinking about the
coronavirus and the vaccine
please focus on the message
we're talking about the blood of jesus
guys
we're talking about the vaccine of
christ
right so just lay aside that for a
second and stay
focused because i have something very
important for you to understand
now
what does this do for us the vaccine of
christ
when it puts us in remission this is
what it means
romans 8 verse 1 the bible says there is
therefore now no condemnation
to them which are in christ jesus who
walk not after the flesh
but after the spirit all right what do
we want to walk in beloved the flesh of
the spirit
we want to walk in the spirit the bible
says for the law of the spirit of life
in christ jesus
has made me free from the law of sin and
death for what the law could not do
in that it was weak through the flesh
god sending his own
son in the likeness of sinful flesh and
forcing
condemned sin in the flesh that the
righteousness of the law
might be fulfilled in us who walk not
after the flesh but after the spirit
in other words the blood of
jesus the blood running through his
veins
was able to live a victorious life
jesus was able to live a victorious life
and now he gives us
that blood that blood
which produces remission in us
that means i'm forgiven by that blood
and i'm enabled
to fulfill the righteousness of the law
how do i know because the verses goes on
to tell me in romans 8 verse 5
for they that are after the flesh do
mind the things of the flesh
but they that are after the spirit the
things of the spirit for to be carnally
minded is death
but to be spiritually minded is life and
peace why
because the carnal mind is enmity
against god
for it is not subject to the law of god
neither indeed can be so watch this guys
the carnal mind does not like the
description of sin
does not want to abide by the
so when christ comes into your life
he allows you to live not in the carnal
mind
but in the spiritual mind and the
spiritual mind
is not at enmity with the law of god
i'm sorry the spiritual mind or the
carnal mind is at enmity with the law of
god
the spiritual mind is not at enmity with
the law of god why
because a spiritual mind
is the mind of christ and the mind of
christ
subjects is is subject to the law of god
in other words the mind of christ obeys
the law of god
just as he said i keep my father's
commandments
so the blood of christ allows us to be
in remission the blood enables us to
walk in the spirit
meaning to be spiritually minded
but there is a problem i know we were
getting happy just now
yes yes yes i want to be in remission we
all want to be in remission praise god
but there is a problem because you see
when you are in remission it does not
mean that you are yet
cured one if you understand what i just
said
when you are in remission it does not
mean
that you are cured
see if any of you know someone that that
may have
cancer or know someone you know that
that had cancer
and you know the terminology when
someone's in remission
we're excited about it but it doesn't
mean that the individual
has been cured the cancer has not been
blotted out one if you get what i'm
saying
see paul wrote these words in romans 7
verse 22 he says for i delight in the
law of god after the inward man
but i see another law in my members
warring against the law of my mind
and bringing me into captivity to the
law of sin which is in my members
o wretched man that i am who shall
deliver me from the body of this
of this death i thank god through jesus
christ our lord
so then with the mind i serve the law of
god but with the
flesh the law of sin see beloved
we're in the flesh and in the flesh the
flesh
desires sin
while we can rejoice that we are in
remission of sins yeah i don't do the
things i used to do
we cannot say that we have been cured of
sin
if any of you say you've been cured of
sin the bible says you made god a liar
we are in remission we have not been
cured of sin why
because the possibility always exists
that you can sin you might sin today
you might sin tomorrow the possibility
is there
when you're when your cancer is in
remission you're keeping it down it's
being held
at bay but you know at any moment
it might come back someone who is cured
of cancer
never has to worry about the cancer
coming back they've been cured
another cancer might come back but it
won't be the same in other words when
you're
cured it is done
it is finished
remember the cancer might come back
when you're in remission it may come
back
when you're cured of it that's a
different story
it is the same thing with sin
right now we are in remission that's why
the bible says
sin is held in check but it is not
totally
eradicated in fact just look at the
world around us
you will see that sin has not been
totally eradicated
this is why the bible tells us in first
timothy 6 12
fight the good fight of faith lay hold
on eternal why are we fighting
what's the fight for if everything is
already done
can you catch what what why are we being
courage to fight
if the battle is done no no no but let
me
we are living in remission of sins right
now praise god
if you've accepted christ you are living
in remission of sins right now but it
does not mean you are
cured of sin
first john 1 9 if we confess our sins
he is faithful and just to forgive us
our sins and to cleanse us from all
unrighteousness
that that's why it's there that's why
that text is there
so that we know that if we fall today or
tomorrow
or the next day we can confess our sins
and be in remission of sins
praise god that we have this
relationship with christ where he he
doesn't say you sin once
then i'm done with you no he says listen
i know you're in remission
and i know how how sin can pop back up
but listen
we're work with something's going to
happen
i'm going to solve this problem
now let me tell you something i'm just
going to diverge for a moment here
because some don't believe in the
vaccine and so they don't get it
they won't get it y'all believe in jesus
come on man he's not real so they don't
believe in the vaccine
others are deceived by a
counterfeit vaccine
yeah yeah yeah there there's a company
it's satan's company and he's selling a
counterfeit
vaccine a vaccine
a gospel that tells you you can do
whatever you want to do
as long as you have this blood you're
inoculated from sin
and even if your sin even if you sin
you're good to go
don't worry about the law of god yeah
the blood gets rid of the law
you can do whatever you want once you
got the blood you're good to go
once saved always saved
beloved satan is selling you a snake oil
gospel
if you believe that
yeah he's selling you a snake oil
gospel he's selling you counterfeit
blood
so remember now matthew
mark luke and john the production of the
vaccine
acts to the book of revelation chapter
the administration of the vaccine
for the remission of sins there is a
third phase to this vaccine
and this third phase introduces us
to revelation chapter 11 verse 18 and 19
it says the nations were angry and thy
wrath is come and the time of the dead
that they should be judged
and that thou should give reward unto
thy servants the prophets and to the
saints and them that fear thy name
small and great and should destroy them
which destroy the earth
and the temple of god was opened in
heaven and there was seen
in his temple the ark of his testament
pause for a second
this is the first time in the book of
revelation
that we are introduced to the most holy
place in fact
it is the first time in the entire new
testament
that we are about to get a view of
events that unfold
under the context of the most holy place
so watch this
from revelation 11 all the way to
revelation 22
revolves around the most holy place
it is christ's most holy place ministry
so let's just juice the entire book of
the new
the entire new testament down just for
recap matthew mark luke and john
the production of the vaccine acts to
revelation chapter 11 the administration
of the vaccine
for the remission of sins and then
revelation
11 all the way to 22 is about
listen carefully the final
blotting out of
the final consummation
or the final restitution of all
things
this is the third phase
of the vaccine of christ and i'm going
to take you back to acts chapter 2
because i want you to see something
acts chapter 2 verse 38
acts chapter 2 verse 38 remember what we
read earlier right
peter said unto them repent and be
baptized
every one of you in the name of jesus
christ for the remission of sins
and you shall receive the gift of the
holy ghost
all right so watch this phase two is the
remission of sins
and you receive the holy ghost
carefully because in acts chapter 3
verse 19
notice what it says acts 3 verse 19
repent ye therefore and be converted
that your sins may be what
blotted out
when the times of refreshing
shall come from the presence of the lord
and he shall send jesus christ which
before was preached unto you
whom the heaven must receive until
the times of restitution of
all things which god has spoken by the
mouth of all his prophets
holy prophets since the world began all
right
let me break this down for you we're
teaching we're teaching
today okay we're teaching
in acts it's repent
and be baptized for the remission
of sins upon the remission of sins we
receive the holy ghost
but in acts 3 he's now saying
repent and be converted
that your sins may be blotted out
when jesus
are you catching this
your sins will be blotted out in
preparation for the
coming of g the blotting out of sins is
connected with the coming of jesus
the remission of sins is connected with
the coming of the holy spirit
one is remission the other is the cure
let me rephrase it phase one
the production of the vaccine matthew
mark luke and john
phase two remission through the vaccine
that's the book of acts that's romans
that's ephesians
all of those books are talking about
we've got a new cure
and it's not the old testament ritual
it's not the sacrifices
it's not the blood of lambs it's the
blood of jesus
and the blood of jesus will send you
into remission
praise god but that's not the complete
story
because from a revelation 11 onward
we now have most holy place
stuff going on and it is dealing with
the final
blotting out and final restitution
of all things
in acts 3 19 when it says he shall
receive or he shall he shall send jesus
christ which before was preached unto
you
whom the heaven must receive until the
times
of restitution of all things what does
it mean the time of restitution of all
things
what is that saying that same word for
restitution
is used in matthew 12 13. then
jesus saved to the man stretched forth
your hand
and he stretched it forth and it was
restored
whole like as the other restored that's
the word
restoration the restitution of all
things is the same as being restored
so god is saying there's coming a time
where all things will be restored
restored to what
restored to its original condition
what was the original condition of earth
and of man
can anyone tell me
the original condition of man the
original condition of this earth
was a world without sin
so the bible is telling us there is
coming a time where all
things will be restored
to the way they were before before what
before
sin the third phase of the
vaccine the blood of christ the
ministration of christ
is to not just put us in remission which
we all are now
but to ultimately cure
us and this planet from
sin one if you understand what i'm
saying
this is going to blow your mind beloved
because this
now is going to give you an even greater
understanding
of daniel chapter 8 verse 13
and 14. listen let me read it in your
hearing
then i heard one saint speaking and
another saint said unto that certain
saint which speak
how long shall be the vision concerning
the daily sacrifice
and the transgression of desolation to
give both the sanctuary and the host to
be trapped under foot
and he said unto me unto 2 300 days
then shall the sanctuary be cleansed
all right i'm going to read the same
verse to you
in three different translations the esv
he said unto me for 2300 evenings in the
mornings
then shall the sanctuary be restored
to its rightful states
the good news bible i heard one i heard
the other angel answered it will
continue for 2 300
evenings and mornings during which the
sacrifice will not be offered
then the temple will be restored
the isv version 2300 days then
what is holy will be restored
let me break this down for you in first
corinthians 6 19 the bible says know you
not that
you are the temple of the holy ghost
if we are a temple what god is trying to
tell us
through the 2300 day prophecy is that
ultimately
god's temples
[Music]
will be cured restored
put back into their original condition
before sin entered
this is the entire purpose behind the
day of atonement
which speaks about the blotting out
of sins one if you
understand what i have shared with you
today
there are three phases to the vaccine of
christ
the first is the production the second
is the remission
and the third is the blotting out the
curing
this is why this is why revelation 3
verse 5 tells us by the way
what is the restitution of all things
what what will be restored
as whole restored as before not only
mankind
those who believe in christ those who
took the vaccine
because some people don't want to take
the vaccine
some people want a vaccine
that they can just claim i i got the
vaccine
do you keep the law of god now no i
don't need to keep the law of god this
vaccine
it's a it's a it's a good kind man with
this vaccine
you don't even need to keep the law of
god and you're good to go
that's a counterfeit vaccine
that's a counterfeit vaccine guy that's
snake oil
you're being sold a counterfeit blood
because the blood of jesus the real
blood of jesus puts you in remission to
sin
meaning when you now see the law of god
you are apt to obey the law you're not
trying to explain away why you don't
need to keep it
you are you are desirous of keeping it
and you
know yes i'm in remission i'm not
perfect you know
i fall i stumble but guess what i'm in
remission
and if i fall and if i stumble i can ask
god for the forgiveness of sins
and i can have the confidence being in
remission
i know that i'm in remission
but i know a time is coming where god is
going to
ultimately cleanse purify
cure us of the sin problem
so those who refuse the cure or who
claim a false cure
this is why the bible says in revelation
3 verse 5 he that overcometh the same
shall be clothed in white raiment and i
will not
blot out his name out of the book of
life
those who refuse the cure are going to
have their names removed
blotted out from the book of life
so we can either have our sins blotted
out or
our names blotted out which one do you
want blotted out
i want my sins blotted out not my name
blotted out
so i want you to notice this the
restoration of all things
means god is gonna consume
and destroy our sins
not only is he putting us in remission
but he's ultimately
going to consume sin and sinners
i want you to notice beloved
daniel 2 verse 44 notice the word i'm
going to keep repeating
in daniel 2 verse 44 and in the days of
these kingdoms shall god
the god of heaven set up a kingdom which
shall never be destroyed
and the kingdom shall not be left to
other people but it shall break in
pieces
and consume
all these kingdoms daniel 7 25
speaking of the little horn he shall
speak great words against the most high
and shall wear out the saints of the
most high and think to change times and
laws
and they shall be given into his hand
until the time times and the dividing of
time
but the judgment shall sit and they
shall take away his dominion
to consume it and destroy it to the end
ii thessalonians 2 verse 8 and then
shall the wicked be
that wicked be revealed whom the lord
shall consume
with the spirit of his mouth and shall
destroy with the brightness of his
coming
isaiah 1 28 and the destruction of the
transgressors
and of the sinners shall be together and
they that forsake the lord
shall be consumed so watch this in the
investigative judgment in the final
blotting out
not only will sin be blotted out but
sinners will be blotted out
those who were not cured
because they took a counterfeit vaccine
beloved this is why god has called his
people to go
preach the everlasting gospel because
what's going out now
is wine the wine of babylon and you know
what wine symbolizes in the bible
jesus used it to symbolize his blood
so so so there are many out there who
are preaching
this false blood selling a counterfeit
wine a counterfeit blood that says hey
drink this man and when you drink it
guess what
the bible says when you drink strong
wine you forget the law of god
that's proverbs
yeah this blood lead you to forget the
law the blood of christ
leads you to keep his commandments
so not only will the will sin be
consumed
but sinners and satan himself will be
this is why daniel 9 26 and 27 says this
listen carefully
and the end thereof shall be with a
flood and until the end of the war
desolations are determined notice the
end of verse 27
and for the overspreading of
abominations he shall make it desolate
even until the consummation
and that determined shall be poured out
upon the desolate
we're talking about the seven last
plagues here
we're talking about the end of the war
we're talking about the consummation
of all things
this is why zephaniah 1 18 says this
neither their silver nor their goals
shall be able to deliver them
in the day of the lord's wrath but the
whole land shall be devoured by the fire
of his jealousy
for he shall make even a speedy
riddance and the word there for riddance
is the same word used in daniel 9 24 for
consummation
he will make a speedy riddance of all
them that dwell on the land
so beloved the consummation is when god
makes a
riddance of sin
and of sinners
we're teaching today i need you to
understand
what the entire new testament is all
about it's about
god trying to explain to us how the
vaccination process works
first it is produced matthew mark luke
and john the 70 week prophecy
then it is administered acts to
revelation chapter 11
which also covers the span of the 1260
years
and then it is that it is administered
for remission of sins
and finally the the final phase of this
vaccination
is the curing of sin
the curing i should say from sin the
blotting out of sin
and of sinners
and the reason why satan doesn't want
the world to understand this
is because he wants them content with
counterfeit blood
a blood that says yeah the sabbath's
been done away with
a blood that says yeah you don't need to
keep the law of god a blood that says
there is no description of sin anymore
all you got to do is just do what you
think is right
and and not do what you think is not
right
that's a counterfeit blood beloved it's
counterfeit wine
it is the wine of babylon
notice name one a verse we all like to
quote
notice the context name one
verse six who can stand before his
indignation
and who can abide in the fierceness of
his anger his
fury is poured out like fire and the
rocks are thrown down by him
the lord is good and a stronghold in a
day of trouble
he knoweth them that trust in him but
watch this
but with an overrunning flood he will
make an
utter end of the place thereof and
darkness shall pursue his enemies does
that sound like daniel 9 to you
an overrunning flood an utter end
utter end
god is going to make an utter end of sin
and we don't need to guess that
because the next verse nahum 1 9
what do you imagine against the lord he
will make an
utter end affliction
shall not rise up the second time
why because it is blotted
out
i've got a few more verses then we're
going to close this up
revelation 14 3 revelation 14
3 describe the redeemed of god
and i want you to notice how their sins
have been blotted out
listen carefully revelation 14 3
and they sung as it were a new song
before the throne
and before the four beasts and the
elders and no man could learn that song
but the 144 thousand which were redeemed
from the earth watch this they were
redeemed from the earth i'm not going to
go into why i believe this is a symbolic
group and not a literal group
not literally 144 000. one of the
reasons simply is because these are they
which are redeemed from the earth
that means those who are redeemed from
the earth are part of this group
notice what it goes on to say verse 4
these are they which were not defiled
with women
for they are virgins again symbolic this
is not 144 000
jewish males this is all symbolic
these are they which follow the lamb
with us of egos these were redeemed
from among men being the first fruits
unto god and to the lamb
and in their mouth listen carefully in
their mouth was found nogal
for they are without fault before the
throne of god
they have been cleansed and purified
and cured of sin
let's back this up in isaiah 44
21 the bible says remember these o jacob
and israel
for thou art my servant i have formed
thee thou art my servant
israel thou shalt not be forgotten of me
i have blotted out
as a thick cloud thy transgressions
and as a cloud thy sins
return unto me for i have
redeemed thee now y'all thinking
oh this happened in the past no listen
look at the next verse sing
o ye heavens for the lord has done it
shout ye lower parts of the earth break
forth in singing ye mountains
o forests and every tree therein for the
lord has redeemed jacob
and glorified himself in israel you know
when this happens
why do you think the 144 000 are singing
because this verse has been fulfilled
at that time their sins have been
blotted out
at that time that's why they're singing
on mount zion
according to isaiah 44 verse 21 and 22
because god has redeemed them from the
earth
this is exactly why revelation 12 11
says
they overcame him who satan by the blood
of the lamb
and by the word of their testimony
let me recap it for you
there are three phases to the vaccine
phase number one was the production of
the vaccine
matthew mark luke and john
phase number two our high priest entered
into the heavenly sanctuary
to begin administering that vaccine
to all who would come to him that is his
holy place phase of ministry
in that phase of ministry we receive
the remission of sins
in which we can have assurance in which
we can
know that we're connected with god in
which we can
rest in peace knowing that we are not in
the condition that we were before
we are in remission but we now
understand we
understand that remission of sins is not
the same thing as being
cured of sin we are only in remission
sin still exists
it is still dwelling in us so
even though in our minds we will to do
what's right
our flesh is still at war with the mind
which means we must realize we're in
remission
we're not cured
acts all the way to revelation 11 is
christ in his holy place ministry
but the final phase of this vaccine
is the blotting out or the consummation
or the restitution of all things to the
way they were before sin
entered this is what the blotting out of
sins is
it is the final phase of christ's
ministry
and this is why god has given a people
a special message to take into the world
hey guys you're on the wrong
blood the vaccine
that you have been using is one that
tells you that the law of god
need not be kept is one that tells you
once you're saved you're always saved
is one that tells you the sabbath part
of the law of god has been done away
with
no no no no the blood of jesus enables
you
to keep those commandments it does not
get rid of those commandments
it gets rid of the old prescription of
sin
why because it is the new prescription
for sin
we have a message to take into the world
and when
this gospel is preached into all the
world
then shall the end come because everyone
who will be vaccinated will be
vaccinated and by the way
this vaccination will keep you from
receiving the mark of the beast
if you are not vaccinated you
will get the mark of the beast i want to
be vaccinated by the blood of jesus
not only do i want the remission of sins
i am looking forward to the blotting out
of sins
and beloved god is trying to show us
step by step
how we are to work in accordance with
the vaccine
let us be about our father's business
beloved and go
on a divine blood drive
to take the true blood of the lamb into
the world
that all who receive it might not only
receive remission of sins
but also receive the blotting out of
sins
to prepare for the coming of jesus
that's what we're told jesus will come
again
and block and and remove our sins and
restore
all things to the way they were before
and if we're not a part of that process
if we're not a part of that process
when jesus comes again he will find us
with sin on us and we will have no
opportunity we will have no chance
because we're told
that he's coming to destroy all that is
unlike him
i hope by the grace of god
you have understood the plan of
salvation
i hope by the grace of god you
understand
the entire new testament just as we
covered the entire old testament last
week
beloved may god bless you and may god
empower you
to live out and to obey and to
plead and to receive this vaccination
heavenly father bless us
cleanse us forgive us
grant us not only remission of sins
but lord ultimately cure us of our sin
problem
in jesus name we pray amen
and amen god bless you
you